A Finding Aid to the Architectural League of New York Records, 1880s-1974, bulk 1927-1968, in the Archives of American Art AAA.archleag
Archives of American Art
- Records Relating to Organizations, 1908-1968, bulk 1930s-1960s; Series 8; 6.1 Linear feet Boxes 95-101
  - Various Organizations, 1908, 1922-1968; 8.3
    - Secretary 1938-1939 (Box 101)
      - Fine Arts Federation, Arch League Representatives, 1939 (Box 101, Folder 19)
      - The Municipal Art Society re: Credit Acknowledgements Labels, 1938-1939 (Box 101, Folder 20)
      - National Council of Architectural Registration Boards, 1939 (Box 101, Folder 21)
      - Society of Designer-Craftsmen, circa 1938-1939 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Secretary 1939-1940 (Box 101)
      - Battery-Brooklyn Bridge, circa 1939 (Box 101, Folder 23)
      - Civil Service Commission, circa 1939 (Box 101, Folder 24)
      - Fine Arts Federation, Representatives, Etc., 1939 (Box 101, Folder 25)
      - The Municipal Art Society, Sale re: "Art in New York" Guides, 1939-1940 (Box 101, Folder 26)
      - School of Living, 1939 (Box 101, Folder 27)
      - U.S. Department of Commerce, 1940 (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - Secretary 1941-1942, National Council of Registration Boards, 1941-1944 (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - Secretary 1941-1942, Record of Postage Used by Various Societies (Monthly), circa 1941-1943 (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - Secretary 1942-1943, Artists for Victory, Inc., circa 1942-1943 (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - Shaker Village, Meetings, 1950s (Box 101, Folder 32)
    - Shaker Village Work Group Meeting, Jerome Count, circa 1958-1965 (Box 101, Folder 33)
    - Snag Club, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 34)
    - The Society of American Etchers, 1942-1944 (Box 101, Folder 35)
    - The Society of Beaux-Arts Architects, 12th Annual Beaux-Arts Ball (Jan. 23, 1931) (Box 101, Folder 36)
    - The Society of Designer-Craftsmen, Agreement, 1936-1938, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 37)
    - Society of Medalists, 1940-1942 (Box 101, Folder 38)
    - Technology Club of New York, 1946-1947 (Box 101, Folder 39)
    - Typophiles, Meetings, 1954-1964 (Box 101, Folder 40)
    - United Public Relations, Meeting, 1958 (Box 101, Folder 41)
    - United Seamen's Service, 1946-1947 (Box 101, Folder 42)
    - Veteran Motor Car Club of America, Meeting, circa 1958-1963 (Box 101, Folder 43)
    - Various (Box 101)
      - Appointments to Other Organizaitons, circa 1937-1945 (Box 101, Folder 44)
      - Charges to Other Societies (Time Sheets) From Apr. 1938, 1938-1939, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 45)
      - Events and Meetings, 1951 (Box 101, Folder 46)
      - Information on Arts Organizations, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 47)
      - Inquiries, 1946-1947 (Box 101, Folder 48)
      - Letters to Clients for New Business, 1952 (Box 101, Folder 49)
      - List of Colleges and Universities, 1940 (Box 101, Folder 50)
      - List of League Members, New York Chapter A.I.A., S.B.A.A., and B.A.I.D., circa 1939 (Box 101, Folder 51)
      - Lists of Other Organizations, 1949, 1952-1953 (Box 101, Folder 52)
      - Organizations Invited to Use Our Facilities, circa 1951 (Box 101, Folder 53)
      - Prospects, 1941, circa 1943 (Box 101, Folder 54)
      - Requests for Next Season Plans, 1954 (Box 101, Folder 55)
      - Societies Affiliated in General Way With the League, 1945 (Box 101, Folder 56)
      - Societies Renting Rooms for Meetings, circa 1939-1941; (3 folders) (Box 101, Folder 57-59)
- Correspondence, 1929-1970; Series 9; 1.85 Linear feet Boxes 101-103, OV 120
  The series is arranged as 2 subseries:
  9.1: Alphabetical, circa 1930s-1970
  9.2: Chronological, 1929-1954
  Found here is miscellaneous correspondence arranged alphabetically by subject or name, and collated correspondence arranged chronologically. Most of the chronological correspondence appears to be Secretaries' files.
  - Alphabetical, circa 1930s-1970; 9.1
    Found is correspondence arranged alphabetically by subject or correspondent's last name.
    - 15 East 48th Street, circa 1940s-1950s; (Oversized material housed in OV 120) (Box 101, Folder 60)
    - Appreciation Letters, 1949 (Box 101, Folder 61)
    - Arwine, Arthur, circa 1942 (Box 101, Folder 62)
    - Bequests to the Architectural League of New York, 1955 (Box 101, Folder 63)
    - Biographies, 1952 (Box 101, Folder 64)
    - [Biographies], 1962 (Box 101, Folder 65)
    - Biographies, Officials, 1952-1953 (Box 101, Folder 66)
    - Brainerd, Harry B., Mailing Privileges and Telephone, 1963 (Box 101, Folder 67)
    - Christmas Carols, 1943-1944 (Box 101, Folder 68)
    - City Planning Commission Notices, 1966-1967 (Box 101, Folder 69)
    - Committee re: Contributions #1 Raffle for Zorn Etching, 1938 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Convalescent Cards [Blank], circa 1930s-1950s (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Eidlitz, French, Fink and Markle - Legal 1950-1951, 1948-1955 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Geiffert, Mr. - 194X, circa 1943 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Geiffert, Mr. - Artists in the Navy, circa 1943 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Gifts to the Architectural League of New York, 1941-1945; (2 folders) (Box 102, Folder 6-7)
    - Goodwill Week, 1949 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Hering, Henry (Estate of), circa 1949 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Hospitalization, 1945 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Hugh Ferriss' Book, 1950s-1960s (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Kleinsinger, Jane - General Correspondence 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Lober, Georg, 1944 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Maps - To Determine Distance for Mileage - Membership, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Oerhle, William, 1940-1943 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - O'Keefe, Mary, 1945-1946 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Publication by Hugh Ferriss 1948-1949 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Questionnaire Returns, circa 1957-1958 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Save Washington Square, 1947 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - Schaefer, Charles (Building Arts), 1964 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - Secretary 1935-1936, Requirements for State Registration of Non-Resident Architects, 1933 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - Secretary 1938-1939 (Box 102)
      - Gifts to the Architectural League of New York, 1939 (Box 102, Folder 22)
      - Resolutions - Letters of Thanks, 1938-1939 (Box 102, Folder 23)
      - Mrs. James C. Rogerson Memorial Service, 1938 (Box 102, Folder 24)
      - Telegrams, 1938-1939 (Box 102, Folder 25)
    - Secretary 1939-1940 (Box 102)
      - Billboard Advertising, 1939 (Box 102, Folder 26)
      - Contributions Solicited, 1939-1940 (Box 102, Folder 27)
      - Telegrams, 1939 (Box 102, Folder 28)
    - Shaw, Sam - Legal Matters, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 29)
    - Stoddard, C.F., Jr., circa 1950s (Box 102, Folder 30)
    - Taft-Hartley Act, 1947 (Box 102, Folder 31)
    - Talent Scout, 1951 (Box 102, Folder 32)
    - Talent Scout Lists Prior to Sept. 1, 1953, circa 1953-1954 (Box 102, Folder 33)
    - Talent Scout Reports, circa 1953-1954 (Box 102, Folder 34)
    - Talent Scout Returns - Sept. 1, 1953 1954 (Box 102, Folder 35)
    - Telegrams, 1940-1962; (3 folders) (Box 102, Folder 36-38)
    - Thank You Letters 1958-1959, circa 1958-1966 (Box 102, Folder 39)
    - Treadwell, Helen, 1950-1951, 1967; (2 folders) (Box 102, Folder 40-41)
    - Von Dexter, Carlos, re: Settlement of Account With the League, 1942-1943 (Box 102, Folder 42)
    - World War II (Box 102)
      - Air Raids, 1942 (Box 102, Folder 43)
      - Civilian Defense, Greville Rickard, Sub-Committee Chairman, 1940-1941 (Box 102, Folder 44)
      - Defense Meeting Per Mr. Woodbridge, 1941-1942 (Box 102, Folder 45)
      - Defense of New York (Correspondence With Secretary of War and Mayor LaGuardia), 1939-1941 (Box 102, Folder 46)
      - Embassy - Grocery, 1943 (Box 102, Folder 47)
      - National Defense (National Census of Engineering and Architectural Personnel), circa 1940 (Box 102, Folder 48)
      - National Defense #2 - Miss Meiere, Chairman, Joint Committee, 1941 (Box 102, Folder 49)
      - Secretary 1941-1943, City Planning Commission re: Post-War Program, 1942 (Box 102, Folder 50)
      - Soldiers and Sailors Monument, 1956 (Box 102, Folder 51)
      - War Memorials, 1945-1948 (Box 102, Folder 52)
      - War Memorials Speeches, 1940s (Box 102, Folder 53)
    - 15 East 48th Street, circa 1940s-1950s; (Oversized material from Box 101, Folder 60) (Box OV 120)
  - Chronological, 1929-1954; 9.2
    Found is correspondence, including Secretary's correspondence, arranged chronologically. It is likely that all of the correspondence in this subseries is Secretary's Files; however, only those specifically labeled as "Secretary" are identified as such in the finding aid.
    - Miscellaneous [Membership Correspondence, circa 1933-1941], S (Box 102, Folder 54)
    - Miscellaneous [Membership Correspondence, circa 1936-1941], A-W, 1929-1941; (9 folders) (Box 102, Folder 55-63)
    - Secretary 1938-1939, A-W, circa 1938-1939; (5 folders) (Box 103, Folder 1-5)
    - Secretary 1939-1940, A-W, 1937-1940; (6 folders) (Box 103, Folder 6-11)
    - Secretary 1941-1942, A-Z, circa 1941-1943 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, H, 1941-1942 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, M, 1941-1943 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, N, 1941-1942 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, G, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous 1949-1950 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, A-W [1950], 1947-1954; (4 folders) (Box 103, Folder 18-21)
    - Miscellaneous, A-W [1951-1952], (5 folders) (Box 103, Folder 22-26)
    - Miscellaneous, B-Z [1952-1953], circa 1951-1954; (5 folders) (Box 103, Folder 27-31)
    - Miscellaneous, B, circa 1952-1954 (Box 103, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous, C, circa 1953-1954 (Box 103, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous, circa 1936-1968; Series 10; 1.3 Linear feet Boxes 103-104
  Folders in this series were collated prior to processing and appear to have been separated from their original files, or were never filed properly. The records have been retained together, rather than interfiled into various series throughout the collection. As such, materials and contents are similar to materials found in other series throughout the collection. There is a significant quantity of correspondence, administrative records, some financial records, and handwritten notes.
  Folders are arranged chronologically.
  - To Be Sorted and Filed, circa 1936-1941 (Box 103, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Letters, 1938-1947 (Box 103, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, File Copies [Executive Secretary's Files?], 1940s-1960s; (2 folders) (Box 103, Folder 36-37)
  - Odds and Ends, 1940s-1966 (Box 103, Folder 38)
  - General, circa 1941-1949 (Box 103, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, General Inquiries, circa 1942-1943 (Box 103, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence re: Hedi Freund Letter (VOA), 1948 (Box 103, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous, 1948-1949 (Box 103, Folder 42)
  - Copies of Miscellaneous Letters, circa 1948-1951; (2 folders) (Box 104, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous Data, circa 1948-1951 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1950s-1960s (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (1950-1951), 1950s-1960s (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1950s-1967 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Data, circa 1952-1953 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Letters Found in Miss Clark's Desk (Oct. 1954), circa 1953-1954 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Letters (1953-1954), circa 1953-1956; (2 folders) (Box 104, Folder 10-11)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, circa 1953-1954 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (1953-1954), circa 1953-1956; (3 folders) (Box 104, Folder 13-15)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1954-1955), circa 1953-1956 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1956-1957), circa 1954-1958 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous (1957), 1956-1958 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1958-1959) [Executive Secretary's Files?], circa 1957-1959 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1959-1960) [Executive Secretary's Files?], circa 1959-1960 (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1960-1961) [Executive Secretary's Files?], circa 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1961-1962), circa 1954-1962 (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence [Executive Committee], 1967 (Box 104, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Data, circa 1967-1968 (Box 104, Folder 24)
- Photographic Materials, 1896-1960s; Series 11; 4.3 Linear feet Boxes 105-108, 112, OVs 121-128
  This series includes black and white photographs, a handful of colored photographs, and negatives of exhibitions, buildings, events, and portraits, as well as scattered related correspondence and printed materials. Also found are nearly 350 lantern slides of buildings, architectural details, and landmarks. Generally, circa dates are based on period indicators in the photographs, such as clothing, car models, etc.
  - "40 Under 40", 1966; (2 folders) (Box 105, Folder 1-2)
  - [37th Annual Exhibition], circa 1922; (Oversized material housed in Box 112, Folder 1) (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - 52nd Annual Exhibition, 1938; (2 folders) (Box 105, Folder 4-5)
  - Annual Exhibition Yearbook, Negatives, circa 1920s (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Architects, Kahn and Jacobs, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Architects, Edward Lehmann, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Architects, Ralph Walker, circa 1960s; (Oversized material housed in Box 112, Folder 2) (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Architectural League of New York Building, circa 1920s-1950s; (Oversized material housed in Box 112, Folder 3) (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - "The Architecture of Trees," Negatives, circa 1960s; (2 folders) (Box 105, Folder 11-12)
  - Correspondence Related to Photographs, 1954 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Designers, E.H. Praeger, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Dinner [House Committee], circa 1950s (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Exhibitions, circa 1920-1925 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Exhibitions: Photographs of Renderings, Murals, Sculptures, Etc., circa 1910s-1940s; (Oversized material housed in Box 112, Folders 4-5) (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Fall Outing (1949) to Philip Johnson's House, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Hugh Ferriss Memorial Exhibition (Feb. 19 - Mar. 8, 1962) (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Greenley, Howard [Architectural League Building], circa 1925; (2 folders) (Box 105, Folder 20-21)
  - Interior Shots, circa 1946-1950 (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - International Fine Arts Council, 1954; (Oversized material housed in Box 112, Folder 6) (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - "The Judgment of Paris" and Miscellaneous, 1914, circa 1920s; (Oversized material housed in Box 112, Folder 7) (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - Lantern Slides, circa 1910s-1940s; (349 slides housed in Boxes 106-107) (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - League Picnic, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - League Seal, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 105, Folder 27)
  - Julian Clarence Levi 90th Birthday Party (Dec. 9, 1964) (Box 105, Folder 28)
  - Marco Polo Extras [House Committee], circa 1950s (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1910s-1930s; (4 folders) (Box 105, Folder 30-33)
  - Miscellaneous Events, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 105, Folder 34)
  - Murals, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 105, Folder 35)
  - [National Gold Medal] Design and Craftsmanship, Robert Sowers, 1950s (Box 105, Folder 36)
  - National Gold Medal Exhibitions, 1945, circa 1960s; (2 folders) (Box 105, Folder 37-38)
  - National Gold Medal Presentation (Mar. 18, 1954) (Box 105, Folder 39)
  - Pan-American Terminal, New York International Airport, circa 1950s (Box 105, Folder 40)
  - Past Presidents, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 105, Folder 41)
  - Past Presidents and Distinguished Members, 1953 (Box 105, Folder 42)
  - Photographers - League Members, 1947-1949 (Box 105, Folder 43)
  - Photographs from a Volume Presented to the League Library by Mr. C. Vanderbilt, 1896; (Oversized material housed in OVs 121-128) (Box 105, Folder 44)
  - Portrait, James Johnson Sweeney, Solomon Guggenheim Museum, 1953 (Box 105, Folder 45)
  - Portrait Committee, circa 1935-1941 (Box 105, Folder 46)
  - Portrait Committee, Horace Moran, Chairman, 1920s-1940s (Box 105, Folder 47)
  - Rollins, Henry; Mills Fellowship in Sculpture, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 48)
  - Samuel Paley Plaza, circa 1960s (Box 105, Folder 49)
  - Sculptors (Box 105)
    - Block, Adolph, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 105, Folder 50)
    - Carr, Sally Swan, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 105, Folder 51)
    - Féron, Louis, 1957 (Box 105, Folder 52)
    - Hancock, Walter, Honorable Mention in Sculpture, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 105, Folder 53)
    - Kreis, Henry, circa 1950s (Box 105, Folder 54)
    - Nivola, Costantino, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 55)
    - Richard, Betti, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 105, Folder 56)
  - Sculptors (Box 108)
    - Rollins, Henry, 1966 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Stevens, Lawrence Tenney, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Zorach, William, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Sculpture Competition, City of New York Department of Public Works, 1957 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Secretary 1941-1942, Harry Townsend's Pictures Called For (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Secretary 1941-1942, Past Presidents and Distinguished Members (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Selections from 1923-1924 Exhibition Catalog, Negatives, circa 1924 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Lantern Slides, circa 1910s-1940s; (3 boxes of lantern slides, Materials from Box 105, Folder 25) (Box 106)
    Cartoons
    Chicago World's Fair
    Drawings
    Floor Plans
    King Solomon's Temple
    Landscapes
    Maps
    Memorials
    Reconstructions and Paintings
    Sections
  - Lantern Slides, circa 1910s-1940s; (2 shoeboxes of lantern slides, Materials from Box 105, Folder 25) (Box 107)
    Aerial
    Banks
    Bridges
    Buildings
    Construction
    Decorations and Objects
    Doors
    Interiors
    Religious Centers
    Residences
    Stadiums
    Theaters
  - [37th Annual Exhibition], circa 1922; (Oversized material from Box 105, Folder 3) (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Architects, Ralph Walker, circa 1960s; (Oversized material from Box 105, Folder 9) (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Architectural League of New York Building, circa 1930s-1950s; (Oversized material from Box 105, Folder 10) (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Exhibitions: Photographs of Renderings, Murals, Sculptures, Etc., circa 1910s-1940s; (2 folders filed at bottom of box due to size, Oversized material from Box 105, Folder 17) (Box 112, Folder 4-5)
  - International Fine Arts Council, 1954; (Oversized material from Box 105, Folder 23) (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - "The Judgment of Paris" and Miscellaneous, 1914, circa 1920s; (Oversized material from Box 105, Folder 24) (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Photographs from a Volume Presented to the League Library by Mr. C. Vanderbilt, 1896; (Oversized material from Box 105, Folder 44) (Box OVs 121-128)
- Scrapbooks, 1880s-1960s; Series 12; 2.2 Linear feet Boxes 108-109, 113-115, BVs 145-148
  Found are eight scrapbooks of clippings from 1880s-1960s, most of which have preservation concerns. Also found are seven scrapbooks of notices and printed materials from the Architectural League of New York from 1925-1930; a scrapbook of signatures of event attendees; a clippings scrapbook compiled by Hamilton M. Wright; and a scrapbook of the Archeological Institute of America.
  Scrapbooks are arranged chronologically.
  - Archeological Institute of America Scrapbook, circa 1880s; (Separated material housed in Box 114, Folder 2) (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Clippings Scrapbooks, 1880s-1890s; (Separated material housed in Box 114, Folder 3) (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Clippings Scrapbooks, circa 1890-1894; (Oversized material housed in Box 113, Folder 1) (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Clippings Scrapbooks, circa 1892-1896; (Separated material housed in Box 115, Folder 1) (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Clippings Scrapbooks, circa 1896-1897; (Separated material housed in Box 115, Folder 2) (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Clippings Scrapbook from Hamilton M. Wright, 1925-1926; (Oversized material housed in Box 113, Folder 2) (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook of Signatures, 1925-1926; (Oversized material housed in Box 113, Folder 3) (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Notices and Printed Materials Scrapbook (Dec. 1925-Dec. 1930), 1925-1930; (2 folders) (Box 108, Folder 15-16)
  - Notices and Printed Materials Scrapbook (Dec. 1925-Dec. 1930), 1925-1930; (5 folders) (Box 109, Folder 1-5)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, circa 1890-1894; (Oversized material from Box 108, Folder 10) (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Clippings Scrapbook from Hamilton M. Wright, 1925-1926; (Oversized material from Box 108, Folder 13) (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook of Signatures, 1925-1926; (Oversized material from Box 108, Folder 14) (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Archeological Institute of America Scrapbook, circa 1880s; (Separated material from Box 108, Folder 8; preservation concern, possible mold) (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1880s-1890s; (Separated material from Box 108, Folder 9; preservation concern, possible mold) (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, circa 1892-1896; (Separated material from Box 108, Folder 11; preservation concern, possible mold) (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, circa 1896-1897; (Separated material from Box 108, Folder 12; preservation concern, possible mold) (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1891-1900 (Box BV 145)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1917-1924 (Box BV 146)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1935-1948 (Box BV 147)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1950s-1960s (Box BV 148)